Before training and deploying a model,
在训练和部署模型之前
we'll need to upload our training data to S3.
我们需要将训练数据上传到 S3
In the last video, I asked you to create
在上个视频中 我请你创建了一个 csv 文件
a CSV file that held are trained features and train labels,
其中包含训练特征和标签
with the train labels in the first column of our CSV file.
第一列是训练标签
Creating a CSV file at a features x and labels y,
创建包含特征 x 和标签 y 的 csv 文件
can be done in a few lines of code.
用几行代码就能搞定
So first, I'm using pd.concat to concatenate my labels with my features.
首先是用 pd.concat 将标签与特征合并到一起
Setting x is equal to 1 means I'm concatenating
将 axis 设为 1
these and smashing them together along the column dimension.
表示沿着列维度合并特征和标签
Then I'm turning this concatenated DataFrame into a CSV file,
然后将合并后的 DataFrame 变成 csv 文件
and passing in where exactly I want this file to be stored,
并传入该文件的存储路径
and I'm specifying that I don't want any headers or indices.
指定不需要任何标题或索引
This ensures that I'm not including anything extraneous,
这样的话 CSV 文件中
like column or row names,
就不包含任何多余信息
in the CSV file,
例如列名或行名
I'm only including the row data.
仅包含原始数据
So if I run this cell,
运行此单元格
I can then test it in the next cell,
然后在下个单元格中测试
and I should see that I've created a train.csv file in my specified data directory.
应该看到在我指定的数据目录下创建了 train.csv 文件
The next step is to actually upload this data to S3.
下一步是将数据上传到 S3
Now, I can do this with a call to session.upload_data.
我可以调用 session.upload_data
We're going to pass in where this data is stored
然后传入数据在本地的存储位置
locally and where I want it to be stored in our S3 bucket.
以及要存储在 S3 存储桶中的哪个位置
So in specifying a different prefix specific to S3,
指定一个不同的 S3 prefix
and they'll even print out where that is.
输出该路径
Here, I can see location in S3 with a bucket name and a specified prefix.
这就是在 S3 中的位置 这是存储桶名称 这是指定的 prefix
Then just to be doubly sure,
再检查一遍
I'm going to iterate through the objects in our S3 bucket and print the contents.
遍历 S3 存储桶中的对象并输出内容
I can see that I have my specified prefix in S3,
这是在 S3 中指定的 prefix
followed by my expected train.csv file.
然后是我的 train.csv 文件
I should also note here that I've been manually navigating to
还要注意 我在每节课之后
S3 to empty my bucket after each lesson,
都手动转到 S3 并清空存储桶
so that I'm not accumulating multiple large model files, for example.
避免积累多个大型模型文件
So if you see multiple files printed out here,
所以如果这里输出多个文件
that could be a sign that you need to empty your S3 bucket.
那么你可能需要清空 S3 存储桶了
Okay. Now that we have data in S3 where an estimator can use it for training,
Ok我们已经将数据上传到 S3，estimator 可以使用这些数据训练模型
next, let's learn more about actually building a custom PyTorch estimator.
下面将学习如何构建一个自定义 PyTorch estimator